Good to have you back, Mr. Harper.
Thank you, Bobby!
We haven't seen your mother here for quite some time.
Well, maybe you just didn't recognize her.
Like Satan, my mother can take many forms!
(chuckles)
Good one!
I'm ready to order.
Of course!
Apologies for the frivolity!
What would you like?
I'll have the seared
ahi tuna fillet.
Hmm... Good choice!
I want it very rare.
That's how we serve it.
I want it red in the
middle, not pink.
Shall do.
If it's pink, don't even
bother bringing it.
Got it.
Just give it to someone who
doesn't know what rare is.
Of course.
You know what? Forget it. You won't get it right.
Is your salmon fresh?
Flown in today.
What time?
I'll ask the chef.
Many forms! Thought you were joking.
Why can't I expose myself
to your kids?
I mean, why can't I meet
your kids?
Please don't make me
hurt your feelings.
You can't hurt my feelings.
All right, fine.
You're a professional boy toy,
a perpetual adolescent leading a dissolute life.
You may have your uses,
but you're not the kind of man I want around my children.
Oh.
What made you think that would
hurt my feelings?
2 O'Clock. Jet Blue from Vancouver.
Would you like me to find out
what the movie was?
Don't bother,
I'll just have the Capellini.
And I'll have the pork chop
with a baked potato.
(Bobby clears throat)
So, yay or nay
on the pork chop?
I'll have the spinach
and goat cheese salad.
-Good choice.
-Thank you.
On the food.
Oh.
Hey, Mom.
Uh, Mom, this is Lydia.
Lydia, my mother.
Oh, pleased to meet you.
Likewise!
Boy, I'm glad I stopped coming to work high.
So, Lydia.
What do you do?
I mean, besides my son.
I'm in real estate.
How interesting, so am I.
Oh, yes. Evelyn Harper.
I recognize you from your bus bench ads.
People all over town are sitting on your face.
Well, dear, maybe someday, if you work hard, people will be sitting on your face, too.
Thank you. Although when I get to be your age,
I hope I won't be schlepping
to open houses
in order to make a buck.
(chuckles)
Don't say 'schlep', darling.
You're a bit too vanilla to pull it off.
So, Charlie, how long have you been seeing this lovely woman?
Uh... how long has it been, sweetie?
Are you telling me you don't remember when we met?
The way he drinks?
There's a good chance he doesn't remember coming down the stairs.
Did his father drink?
What choice did he have?
Charlie, don't be snide.
And stand up straight.
This is so weird.
EVELYN:
Well, I really must run.
Oh, me too. Can I walk you out?
Oh, how nice.
Are you sure you don't want to stay and finish putting on your makeup?
That's okay, I'm done.
Would you like to borrow some?
No, thanks, I'm allergic to the drugstore brands.
What?
And they call you slow.
You're kidding, right?
You don't see it?
See what?
Lydia and Mom.
What about them?
Come on, Charlie.
The only difference between those two broads is you came out of one and...
CHARLIE:
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on, hold on.
You think Lydia's like Mom?
No. We think Lydia is Mom.
Okay, okay, you guys are nuts.
This conversation
is over.
Who calls me slow?